Thank you for watching!
Here we go again, it's starting.
It's time for another episode of "Halo! Stay, this time with Rei Inoue from JuiceJuice and Akari Endo from JuiceJuice!
This time, we will be presenting with these two, so please bear with us until the end. Please bear with me until the end.
Today, JuiceJuice released the best selection album "Juice Story" to commemorate the 10th anniversary of JuiceJuice. Yay! Thank you very much.
It's a best selection album, so it's a collection of 13 songs from Elisuguri.
All of the songs were self-remade and recorded on sileck, and the orchestrations were also changed a bit.
And there is one new song in the album, BON VOYAGE.
There is a song called "BON VOYAGE" (Trail of Thoughts).
Yes, this song has very positive lyrics, and I personally think it's very beautiful.
There is a scene where Ms. Kazuha Arisase is playing the violin, and her tone is really beautiful.
I would like you to listen to it with all your ears.
And I heard that she thought up the melody and recorded it herself, so I think it really shows her personality.
I think it will be a very memorable song for Uemura-san as well.
I also tried to think about how I wanted to sing this song during the recording process, so when you listen to it, I hope you will enjoy it as much as I did.
When you listen to the songs, I hope you will find many good things about the members and listen to them.
You have started a tour with the same title as this album.
Juice-Tory
How is it going?
Well, Juice-Tory is meant to show the history of Juice.
The setlist is the same, and the theme of this tour is our explosive power, so we are trying our best to bring our power to you.
We are trying our best to deliver power to you with our explosive power.
And now that Miki Kawashima has joined the group, I have become a senior member.
Miki Kawashima is very cool and has a wonderful singing voice.
I have to do my best not to lose to her.
I will do my best.
Now, please watch this video.
Thank you for watching!
"I can live on my own." Is that a compliment?
Somebody should do something about my stubborn heart.I've got a stubborn heart. Somebody do something about it.
I can't do this without you.
Tearful, hero of the drama
I cried and I cried and I cried and I cried and I cried and I cried
I'm so blinded by the glare I can't look away
I'm going to be happy, even if it's just for a little while longer.
Put on your standard mask. It's an unfair world out there.
I guess I can live on my own. Is that a compliment?
Is that a compliment?
I'm counting on you. Is that a compliment?
Can someone please tell me what's in your heart that's leading you away?
I'm really a lonely person.
I'd like to give a little away.
But I'm the only one who can make myself happy
I'm the only one who can make myself happy.
I have to be brave
I can't live alone
So, you know, I admire it.
I'm just being stubborn... and weak.
Someone should see me for what I am.
In a time when there's no such thing as a reliable oencista...
In a time when there's nowhere left to go
To the force that pushes forward so bitterly
I can live on my own
Is that a compliment?
Weakness that hides strength
Will someone please see through that?
I'm counting on you.
That's not a compliment.
Don't be so stubborn. I don't have a stubborn heart.
Somebody do something about it.
I can live on my own.
That would be nice.
I know, right? Be me, be me, be me.
I want to hug someone.
Having fun? Watch the rest of the show!
This is Halo with Reine Inoue and Akari Endo of Juice Juice! Stay!
I'm going to ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly.
I'll do my best. Okay, here we go.
So, Shuri, you've recently become interested in arranging hair. What kind of arrangement are you secretly practicing?
Curly hair.
Deren It's been about a year since you joined Juice Juice. What's the biggest change in yourself?
I've become closer to my seniors.
Deren, what kind of work do you want to do now?
I would like to work with Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume。 Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume。ヌ23 and Sakura Ishiyama of Juice Juice, I want to hold an event with them.
Deren, if you were to go out to eat with me, what would you like to eat?
Spaghetti with cod roe.
Oh, that sounds great!
This year is the 25th anniversary of Hello! Project. What song best fits Akari's motto of "work hard"?
Shalala by Kobushi Factory.
Ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
Wow, the tempo was really good.
I thought it was a nice touch.
First of all, you've been arranging your hair lately, haven't you?
I'm into curly hair.
Not secretly, but...
I've been curling my hair a little more.
I have a lot of hair.
It's very hard to curl it. It's a little bit hard to wind up.
It takes a lot of time.
I'm going to keep working hard to roll in those parts gradually
I'm going to keep working on it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I want to do something for her.
I can't do hair, but...
I can't do hair, but I can do makeup.
I want you to do it.
I'd like to try it.
I also asked you if you would go out to eat with me.
I asked her if she'd go out to eat with me.
I've been saying that we should go out for ice cream.
I've been saying it too much and now the ice cream season is ending.
I've been saying it too much and now the ice cream season is over.
I was just saying that it might be a surprise.
We were talking about this earlier.
Cod roe pasta
I really like it.
I heard that you like it too.
I love it!
Let's go eat it!
I love it so much that I'm going on a cod roe pasta tour!
Please let me tag along next time!
Don't be too hard on yourself.
I'm sure I'll post about it on SNS when I get there.
Questions for Mr. Igawa will be posted after the VTR.
Hello! Wake up call
Wake up call It's time to wake up It's time to enjoy life The sun is in my heart Just do it, just do it, just do it, just do it
Someone's heart is waiting for the morning at the bottom of the night I'll shine my light on it Someone's heart at the bottom of the night, waiting for the morning, I'll light it up
Morning Musume。 23
Wake up call Wake up time
October 25 on SAIL
Next, I would like to ask Inoue-san a question.
Let's go!
Speaking of Pirin Inoue-san, what is your favorite chocolate these days?
It's Lotte's almond chocolate with crunch!
PirinWhat is the strong point of the current 11-member group from JuiceJuice Inoue's point of view?
Well, I guess it's the depth of our voices since we have 11 members.
PirinWhat is your hair care philosophy?
The degree of dryness varies from time to time.
I use milk when there is not enough moisture, and oil when there is not enough oil.
PirinWhat was your most memorable moment at the Hello!
Being able to dance the year in JuiceJuice!
PirinWhich song from Hello! Project's history would you like to cover with JuiceJuice?
Bravo Bravo by Bono.
PirinWhat is your favorite chocolate?
Chocolate? My favorite chocolate?
You eat it all the time.
I had some with me today.
It came out of my bag just like that.
It's always there.
I always see it on your desk.
I'd like to go to Itamizaki someday.
I'd like to go to Itamizaki one day.
I don't care when, I don't care if it's now.
I'll get on it.
Project's 25th anniversary concert the other day, and one of the things that struck me was that year says year.
Yes, sir. Yes, I did.
I've heard from a lot of fans that it was really good.
When I saw the setlist, I thought I was looking at the wrong thing.
I thought it was the juice.
But there were many members who told me they liked Fist in the Juice too.
I was so happy and at the same time, each member sang in a different way.
I was thinking how great Juice is.
I was able to put a lot of energy into my performance.
I was also impressed by the way they took care of their hair, which changed from day to day.
I don't have a lot of hair, but it gets damaged easily.
So I have to take really good care of my hair, otherwise I wouldn't be able to do it anymore.
That's a little surprising.
You're kidding?
It's always shiny.
What? Thank you.
I'm glad.
I've been thinking about it for a while, so I'm going to change it depending on the day.
I'll try to change it on those days.
Hello! Stee, we'll continue after this.
Bye bye!
Se-no
Cute!
Black Lounds, Beaune.
Black Lounds Nanamaria
Kopunkah!
It's another day on the train to school
Still, it's not hard
In the usual place in the usual car
Can I meet that boy I'm interested in?
The boy with glasses whose name I don't even knowA boy with glasses whose name I don't even know
In the same car at the same time
The chimirabi boy I always see
just a little this morning
Ah, the boy with glasses, glasses
The boy with a gentle look
Ah, the boy with glasses and spectacles
Please, please, please
Ready!
Like a scarecrow
The boy with the crow's veil
Ah, the boy with the glasses!
Please, please, please!
Ready!
Like a Scarecrow
How long has it been?
When was the last time I saw you every morning?
I wonder if you moved somewhere else.
I find myself looking for today's today.
Then, I was late and just barely missed the train.
I found you in a different car than usual.
The departure was fixed, but it was dark.
I don't think so... my eyes are out of my head...
You've changed your image... next to you...
Who's that pretty, smiling girl next to you?
Who's that cute, smiling girl next to you? Who's that cute, smiling girl next to you?
He's always been the boy with the catchy face.
But now he's wearing glasses.
She's not wearing makeup.
Oh, my God, you guys look so happy. the crow bell boy looks happy
Crow's bell boy.
But glasses. Now I'm like this.
I'm like this when I take off my glasses
I want to be loved more than I've ever loved anyone
I want to be loved
That's all for now, Beyonce!
I'm sorry!
Bye bye!
Big one!
Wow! Wow!
Oh, my gosh!
Here come the prawns!
It's really coming!
Shrimp!
Wow! Oh, my gosh!
Wow! Wow!
Guntherwell tanker!
Looks yummy!
Next up was a presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart. Yay!
Project has many lyrics that touch our hearts, but the other day was a sports day, so I would like to share with you some lyrics and phrases that are perfect for physical exercises.
Okay, Inoue, let's start.
I am ℃-ute-san. I would like to recommend "Iron Heart" by ℃-ute.
The chorus of "Iron Heart" is very similar to the chorus of the song. The chorus of the song says, "Run through, iron heart, burn hot, iron heart," so I hope everyone's bodies and hearts will burn hot as well.
The choreography of the chorus is also about running with your feet like this, so I think it would be good to run, or if you are a hurdle runner, you can jump up and down with a "Hurray! If you are running hurdles, I would like to see you jump up and down with a "Hurray!
If you are doing hurdle running, I would be happy if you could jump with a "Hurray! If you are doing hurdle running, I would like you to run as fast as you can.
You will sweat twice as much as usual.
I think this is a song that will challenge you seriously.
I am cheering for you. We support you.
Now please watch the VTR. Please watch the VTR.
Presentation of lyrics that touched my heart
In this corner, we would like to present the lyrics of the songs of Hello!
Project's songs and talk about the charm of the lyrics. Project's songs and talk about their charms.
This week, I, Tani Tani, will be presenting.
So, here it is.
I will read it.
Let's count what we can do, so we don't become wimps.
You see, I have to be more proud of myself.
I chose these lyrics because they make me feel positive.
I see. It's a good lyric, isn't it?
I think it's a really good lyric, and I'm sure it's a journey to fill in the missing pieces.
The lyrics resonate more with me because of the eye contact with the members, and sometimes they get a little too loud.
Kiki Asakura and I performed this song at a fan club event with the three of us, right?
And we sang this song, and the lyrics really resonated with me.
I was deeply moved by the lyrics as I sang it.
There are other great lyrics, too.
There's another lyric that says, "Let's change 'I'm sorry' to 'thank you.
The lyrics are also really good, and after I heard the lyrics, I often say "excuse me" to store clerks and such.
I stopped saying "I'm sorry" as a reflex and just said "thank you".
It made me feel a little better, so please give it a try!
So, please look forward to the next issue!
This time, Rei Inoue and Akari Endo of Juice-Juice will be presenting "Halo! STE, presented by Reie Inoue and Akari Endo of Juice-Juice.
As I mentioned in the opening, today, October 11, Juice-Juice's 10th anniversary best selection album "Juice-Tory" will be released.
Juice-Juice's 10th anniversary best selection album, Juice-Tory, has been released!
I would like to talk a little about this Juice-Tory, and I would like to share with you some of the points that impressed me personally or that I was particular about.
I'd like to talk a little about Juice-Tory, but I'd like to share with you some of the points that impressed me personally, or that I was particular about.
I had been listening to it thinking it was really cool, but when I listened to another version, I thought it was possible to do it this way, too.
The BPM hasn't changed at all, but the groove of the instruments makes such a difference, and that's why I recorded the song. The BPM did not change at all, but the groove of the instruments made such a difference in the recording.
I sing a cappella at the beginning of Wonderful World.
That was really....
It's hard to believe that there are 11 of us, and we all sound so beautiful together.
I hope you will listen carefully to those parts, and I'm looking forward to hearing each voice.
Wow, you can do that among 11 people? That's right.
Some of them are a little difficult.
I would like to try it myself.
I would like to try it too.
And also, in this album, the older team and the younger team sang one song each,
My older team sings Black Butterfly.
I had been listening to the voices of the original members and learning how they sang like this,
I was learning how to sing like this by listening to the voices of the original members and studying how they sang,
It was difficult for me to sing in my own way on recordings,
But when I heard the cheers, I thought it was really cool,
The younger team sang for the first time in their experience.
The younger team is singing for the first time. They are trying their best in that song, but there is a part where they start to sound like lines during the interlude,
If I'm not careful, I get carried away by the feeling of embarrassment,
But in those moments, I just let go of my emotions and say the lines as boldly as I can, and I hope you enjoy the song.
I hope you will listen to it. It's really cute, so please listen to it.
I hope you will find the goodness in each of the 11 members of the new JuiceJuice, and I hope you will also notice the changes from the past.
You can already hear this song on the tour, so let's enjoy the tour together.
Halo! STE!
Just a month ago, I attended the Hello! Project 25th Anniversary Concert was held just a month ago.
Looking back on those two days, was there anything memorable? I guess so.
I have always admired Cute and have been active in the project for a long time,
Kobushi Factory was originally created to carry on the spirit of Berryz KOBO,
I was really moved by the fact that Berryz KOBO was singing with us, and I watched the whole show,
I was probably feeling the same way as everyone else who was there,
I was able to take pictures with them in between the performances and afterwards, I was able to take pictures with her between stages and after the show,
Airi Suzuki talked to me a lot,
I sang "Nen ni Nen" at the same performance,
I sang "Nen ni Nen" at the same performance, so she told me how cool I was,
The day before, I sang Hatsukoe Cider,
I sang the first part of the song,
I sang the first part of the song, so he said he wanted to see it,
I was a little too excited to see the first part of the song, but I guess that's what happens when you have a wide-angle view,
Project 25th Anniversary Concert,
Project 25th Anniversary Concert.
This time, I would like to show you the song "Platonic Planet" from Hello!
I was given a very premium opportunity to perform with Juice-Juice and the prince, Yuka Miyazaki, Yoshikazu Miyamoto, and Aika Inaba,
For me personally, it was the first time to sing with Ms. Miyazaki as Juice-Juice.
So I was a little nervous,
I think I probably talked to Ms. Miyazaki the most during the rehearsal,
I was so happy that Mr. Miyazaki was so frank and friendly with me.
I was very happy.
It was the first time for me to work with Oji-san.
I have worked with Miyazaki-san once in a one plus one situation, but it was my first time with other senior actors,
I was very nervous from the beginning of the rehearsal.
That's right.
I was very nervous, but I couldn't believe that we were performing together.
It felt like it was the real thing.
It was so wonderful that I was almost moved to tears.
It was so wonderful, I was almost in tears.
I was almost in tears, but it was a really cool song, so I decided to go for it and did my best.
Yes, we did our best. We did our best.
We did our best.
Please have a look.
Please take a look.Go ahead.
I I I I I
Love, love, love, love, love, love, love
Love
Later Ise
Isn't it a little bit nice?
Wow, wow, wow. Look at you.
You're doing great.
But, but...
Today's the day to cry.
Wow, wow, wow, maybe I'll make a face with my heart
Come on Come on If the blue of this star
If it's gonna cool my fever
I'd like to take you with me
I want to take you with me all the way to life
Come on already
It has to be you, it has to be you
Jump out of the car and go protoike
I want to see the amazing world
You'll see it with your own eyes
You'll see.
I'm better than you.
Smiling platonic
I'm gonna hug you back.
I can't forgive everything
Love, love, love, love, love
Love, love, love, love, love, love
Love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love
Prometheum, I gently lit her heart on fire.Prometheum. I gently lit a fire in my chest.
Even if it's just once more.
Once you know, you can't go back.
Countdown
The apple kissed this star, and it was born with color.
Surely if you and I look at each other, Genesis is destiny
I can't stand it at all, just a little bit, get out of the way, platonic
I don't want words, but I want a promise
I'm not sure I'm aware of it, but I'm pretending I'm not, and it's not logical.
I don't know if you're aware of it, but if you pretend to be, please stop trying to reason with me.
Subtitle Kiminomiya
Jump out and platonic start
I want to show you all the time, but I want to believe you.
You can see it in my eyes
I'm definitely better than you
Platonic start smiling
I'll hug you back
I'll love you for everything
I can't forgive you
Love, love, love, love, love
Let's work together
Juice-Juice's Inomerite Akari Endo presents Halo! Sta!" by Juice-Juice's Inomerite Endo Akari.
It's time for us to say goodbye, so here's an announcement.
As I've told you before, today, October 11th.
Juice-Juice, the best selection album commemorating our 10th anniversary, has been released!
Well, I've already told you a lot about it, so I hope you can understand the appeal of the album.
I'm sure you can understand the appeal of this album, but listening to it with your ears is totally different from listening to it with words, so please get it and listen to it.
I hope you will get it and listen to it a lot!
And Juice-Juice 10th Anniversary Concert Tour
DVD and Blu-ray of Juice-Juice at Budokan will be released on December 6!DVD and Blu-ray of Juice-Juice at Budokan will be released on December 6!
I don't know if the people who came to the concert back then miss it or not.
I don't know.
I don't know, I guess everyone has their own feeling.
I think we probably feel nostalgic.
I think they have grown up since then.
I think they look so cute with their makeup.
I'd like to see them too.
Juice-Juice 10th Anniversary Concert Tour 2023Juice Story is now underway.
This weekend will be at Kanagawa Zama Park!
The songs from the album are sung very well.
I've already told you what I want you to pay attention to.
We hope you'll pay attention to the songs on the album!
And on November 23rd, I will be performing at Fruit Zipper Juice- Juice- Juice!
It's called Fruit Juice, which is a cute name.
I think it's a great name for such a great combination, and I think it's wonderful at that point.
Please look forward to it on the 23rd!
And on November 26th, I will be performing at the Chikappa Festival 2023 with Tsubaki Factory!
I'm looking forward to having a lot of fun at this festival!
I'm looking forward to it! Project members will be appearing on the channel!
New videos are uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel!
This time I'm joined by Rei Inoue and Akari Endo from Juice-Juice!
Good bye!
Thank you for watching!